(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
清廉なるHeretics
Seiren Naru Heretics
焚き火 掲げて
Holding up a bonfire,
立ち止まっているの
are you standing still?
...いるの
...still?
数え出して
Start counting,
痛みの数なんだっつー
it's the number of pains.
眠るまで ずっと
Until I fall asleep, forever.
黒い 鳥が飛んで見えた
I saw a black bird fly by.
小さな猫をさらって消えてった
It snatched a small cat and disappeared.
心が千切れるまま 叫ぶ
Screaming as my heart is torn apart,
その 報いを
for that retribution.
いつか 曖昧なままで隠した
Someday, hidden away in vagueness,
虹の中へ
into the rainbow.
抱いた 日がまた 私を焦がすなら
If the day I held it burns me again,
愛を 探して 巡る星
searching for love, the wandering stars,
希望を待って
waiting for hope.
泣いた 日々がまた 崩れ落ちたとしても
Even if the crying days crumble away again.
焚き火 壊して
Destroy the bonfire,
誰か つながっているの
is someone connected?
...いるの
...connected?
数え出して
Start counting,
失敗 ばかり 語る
talking only about failures.
偽物の宇宙壊せ
Destroy the fake universe.
黒い 渦が巻いて見えた
I saw a black vortex swirling.
小さな 苦しみだけ 消えてった
Only small sufferings disappeared.
言葉にできなかったから
Because I couldn't put it into words.
…真っ向喰うを
…devouring it head-on
いつか愛を連れ出して　不甲斐ないから及びを捨てて
Someday I'll lead love away,
since I'm pathetic, I'll cast away my reach
大体　痛み回って　私は解くから
Pain mostly circulates,
since I will solve it
愛を探して　巡る本気　星を追って
Searching for love,
chasing the serious stars as they turn
泣いた日々がまた　重んで消えようとしても
Even if the days I cried pile up
and try to disappear again
まだ終われないから
Because it's not over yet
また焔が立ち昇り出す
The flames begin to rise again
いつか曖昧なままで　なくしたイメージの中へ
Someday, remaining ambiguous,
into the lost image
だいたい光待って　私は焦がすから
Mostly waiting for the light,
since I will scorch it
愛を探して　巡る本気　星を追って
Searching for love,
chasing the serious stars as they turn
繋いだ手はまた　ずっと放さないまま
The hands we joined,
I won't let go of them for a long time
愛を連れ出して　不甲斐ないから及びを捨てて
Taking love away,
since I'm pathetic, I'll cast away my reach
大体　痛み回って　私は解くから
Pain mostly circulates,
since I will solve it
愛を探して　巡る本気　星を追って
Searching for love,
chasing the serious stars as they turn
泣いた日々がまた　重んで消えようとしても
Even if the days I cried pile up
and try to disappear again
消えようとしても
Even if it tries to disappear
離さないから
Because I won't let go
消えようとしても
Even if it tries to disappear
離さないから
Because I won't let go
ninelie
Lyrics・Music: 澤野弘之
Lyrics・Music: Hiroyuki Sawano
君を繋ぐ空の星が一つ　音を立てても
Even if one star in the sky
that connects you makes a sound
どれも同じ雨に濡れた夢ばかり　乾くだけの鼓動
Every single one is a dream drenched in the same rain,
a heartbeat that only withers
相手をなぞる答えに疲れた
I'm tired of the answers
that trace my partner
繰り返す言い訳に崩れた朝
A morning that crumbled
into repeating excuses
掴めないデイドリーム　手をくれたストーリーと
An unreachable daydream,
with the story that lent a hand
栄光が何処へ　叫び唱えても
No matter how much I shout and chant
where the glory went
荒れたZoneは前も潜れない
I can't even dive into the rough Zone anymore
だからSilence　灯すThe melody
So, Silence, the melody that lights up
そっと歯車のように嵌まるピースが　疼こうとしても
Even if the pieces that fit like gears
quietly try to ache
絵もない偽りと同じ　黄昏に並ぶだけの証
The same as a pictureless lie,
evidence that only lines up in the twilight
箱の中に揃えた苛立ち
Irritation gathered inside a box
順番待ちさらし　誤魔化しの鼓動
Exposed while waiting in line,
a heartbeat of deception
Don't be afraid, daybreak has come.
Daydream, 遠く去った あの日のヴィジョン
Daydream, the vision of that day gone far away
君の夢が 横で外れても
Even if your dream goes astray beside me
僕は歌い 橋を架けよう
I will sing and build a bridge
だからSilence 鳴らすな 鼓動
So Silence, don't let the heartbeat sound
どこまでも 高架線沿ったリズム
A rhythm along the elevated tracks forever
過ぎた街並みは 終わりの合図と溶け
The passing townscape melts with the signal of the end
伝えない ディザミかけのイメージに
Into an inexpressible, half-disassembled image
目が覚めてゆく 孤独のショート
Waking up from a short moment of solitude
砕けた Crying dream 飛び立った 逆相の間違い
A broken Crying dream, a mistake of running in the opposite direction taking flight
誘い 溺れ はしゃいでても
Even if I'm lured, drowning, and frolicking
僕は歌い 舵を捨てよう
I will sing and throw away the helm
だからSilence 響くな 鼓動
So Silence, don't let the heartbeat echo
Don't be afraid, daybreak has come.
LET IT OUT
Lyrics:福原美穂 Music:福原美穂・山口寛雄
Lyrics: Miho Fukuhara Music: Miho Fukuhara, Hiroo Yamaguchi
Let it all out, Let it all out.
強がらなくていいんだね
You don't have to pretend to be strong
誰かが描いてた 壁の落書きの花が揺れる
Flowers in graffiti on a wall someone drew are swaying
自分らしさなんて 誰もわからないよ
No one knows what it means to be "yourself"
長い長い道の途中で 無くしたり 拾ったり
Losing things, picking things up on a long, long road
急に寂しくなって 泣いちゃう日もあるけど
There are days when I suddenly feel lonely and cry, but...
涙も痛みも 星に替えよう
Let's turn tears and pain into stars
明日を照らす 灯をともそう
Let's light a flame that illuminates tomorrow
小さな迷いも 二人で創ろう
Let's create even small hesitations together
星屑を 強く光る 永久（とわ）を咲かそう
Let's make the stardust shine brightly and let eternity bloom
Let it all out, Let it all out.
足りないことだらけよね
It's full of things that are lacking, isn't it?
足りなくていいんだね
It's okay to be lacking
だから君と出会えたんだ
That's why I was able to meet you
「確か」が何なのか それが知りたくて
I wanted to know what "certainty" was
小さなナイフを 靴の下に隠してた
I hid a small knife under my shoe
強がってついた 嘘のほうがずっと痛かった
The lies I told while acting strong hurt much more
本当は怖いよ だけど生きてゆく
I'm actually scared, but I'll keep living
笑顔の君を 風が撫でてゆく
The wind strokes you as you smile
小さな手かざして 二人で創ろう
Holding up our small hands, let's create together
星屑を 強く光る 永久（とわ）を咲かそう
Let's make the stardust shine brightly and let eternity bloom
正しいことが間違ってたらどうすればいい？
What should I do if the right thing is wrong?
悲しいことが正しかったら受け入れるだけ？
If sad things are right, do I just accept them?
失くしたと思ってた でも君が知ってた
I thought I lost it, but you knew
君がいて本当に良かった
I'm really glad you were here
Ah...
意地も痛みも 星に変えよう
Let's turn our stubbornness and pain into stars.
明日を照らす明かりを灯そう
Let's light the lamp that illuminates tomorrow.
小さな手かざして 二人で創ろう
With our small hands held up, let's create together.
星屑を 強く光る永遠を
Stardust, an eternity that shines brightly.
さよなら いつかは 来るかもしれない
A farewell might come one day.
季節は それでも 巡り巡ってゆく
Even so, the seasons will keep on turning.
小さく迷っても 歩いてく君と
Even with small hesitations, I'll walk with you.
歩いてく 空だけは変わらないでいてね
I'll keep walking, just please let the sky stay the same.
晴る
Lyrics ・ Music : n-buna
Sunny (Haruru)
あなたは風のように
You are like the wind.
目を閉じては夕暮れ
Closing your eyes, it's twilight.
何を思っているのだろうか
I wonder what you're thinking about.
瞼を開いていた
Your eyelids were open.
あなたの目に色付いた
Colors appeared in your eyes.
少しだけ春の匂いがした
There was a faint scent of spring.
晴れに晴れ、花よ咲け
Shine and shine, flowers bloom.
咲いて晴れのせ
Blooming, all because of the sun.
降り止めば雨でさえ
Even the rain, once it stops...
あなたを飾る晴る
...becomes the sun that adorns you.
胸を打つ音よ鳴れ
Let the sound that strikes the heart ring out.
僕ら晴れ風
We are the sunny breeze.
あの雲も払ってゆけ
Go and brush away those clouds.
遠くまで、遠くまで
To the far distance, far away.
あなたは晴れ模様に
You, in a sunny mood.
目を閉じては青色
Closing your eyes, it's blue.
何か悲しいのだろうか
I wonder if something is sad.
瞼を開いている
Your eyelids are open.
あなたの目に色付いた
Colors appeared in your eyes.
今少し、雨の匂いがした
Just now, there was a faint scent of rain.
泣きに泣け、空よ泣け
Cry and cry, sky cry out.
泣いて雨のせ
Crying, all because of the rain.
降り頻る雨でさえ
Even the pouring rain...
雲の上では晴る
...is sunny above the clouds.
土を打つ音よ鳴れ
Let the sound that strikes the earth ring out.
僕ら晴れ割れ
We are the sunny break.
あの海も払ってゆけ
Go and brush away that sea.
遠くまで、遠くまで
To the far distance, far away.
通り雨、草を靡かせ
A passing shower, making the grass sway.
土、雲、あれも晴るのせい
The earth, the clouds, those too are because of the sun.
風のよう、胸に晴るのせい
Like the wind, the sun in my heart is the cause.
晴るを待つ
Waiting for the sun.
晴れに晴れ、空よ咲け
Shine and shine, sky bloom.
咲いて晴れのせ
Blooming, all because of the sun.
降り止めば雨でさえ
Even the rain, once it stops...
あなたを
...you.
僕らはずっと 晴るを待つ
We've been waiting for clear skies all along
胸を打つ音奏でて
Playing the beats that strike our hearts
僕ら晴る風
We are the breeze of clear skies
音に聞く晴るの風
The breeze of clear skies we hear in the sound
さあこの歌よ凪げ
Now, may this song bring a calm
晴れに晴れ 花よ咲け
Clearing and clearing, let the flowers bloom
咲いて晴るのせい
Bloom, because of the clear skies
あの雲も越えてゆけ
Go even beyond those clouds
遠くまで 遠くまで
To somewhere far away, far away
memories
Lyrics: 大槻真希 Music: 森純太
Lyrics: Maki Otsuki Music: Junta Mori
小さな頃には 宝の地図が
When I was little, a treasure map
頭の中に 浮かんでいて
Would float around in my head
いつでも探した 奇跡の場所を
I was always searching for that place of miracles
知らない誰かに 負けないように
So I wouldn't lose to anyone I didn't know
La la la...
今では
But now
埃だらけの毎日
Every day is covered in dust
いつの日か 全ての
One day, I'll just surrender
時に身をまかせるだけ
Myself to the flow of time
もしも世界が変わるのなら
If the world were to change
何も知らない頃の私に
Take me back to the time when I didn't know anything
連れていって 思い出が
Take me back so that my memories
色あせないように
Never fade away
小さな頃から 歌を歌って
I've been singing songs since I was little
夢見る心 温めてた
Warming my dreaming heart
みんなで真似した 秘密のメロディ
The secret melody we all used to imitate
今度は上手に 聞こえるように
Hoping it'll sound better this time
La la la...
今では
But now
ため息ついてばかりで
I'm doing nothing but sighing
誰もまだ 本当の
And still no one is able
夢さえつかめないまま
To grasp their true dreams
もしも時代が戻るのなら
If time were to turn back
涙を知った頃の私に
Take me back to the time when I first learned of tears
連れていって せつなさが
Take me back so that this sadness
追いつかないように
Can't catch up to me
もしも世界が変わるのなら
If the world were to change
何も知らない頃の私に
Take me back to the time when I didn't know anything
連れていって 思い出が
Take me back so that my memories
色あせないように
Never fade away
連れていって せつなさが
Take me back so that this sadness
追いつかないように
Can't catch up to me
ぼくらのレットイットビー
Our Let It Be
Lyrics・Music: 針原翼（はりーP）
Lyrics・Music: Tsubasa Harihara (Harii-P)
生まれ変われるのなら
If I could be reborn
目印になるから待っていてよ
I'll become a signpost, so please wait for me
小指と小指の長い糸
The long thread between our pinkies
解けないように結んでおこう
Let's tie it so it won't come undone
夏祭り
Summer festival
天気雨降り
A sunshower falls
空に
In the sky...
地図がかかるころなの
...it's around the time a map hangs
凍った感情が
Frozen emotions
いつか君を消していく
Will one day erase you
言えなくなると
When words go unsaid
灯し守れる魂火
A soul fire we can keep lit and protect
でも独りじゃないと
But because you're not alone
解け落ちていないから
Because it hasn't unraveled and fallen
また僕たちは出会う時が来る
The time for us to meet again will come
きっと
Surely
僕ら大人になったら
When we grow up
正義のヒーローになるんだ
We'll become heroes of justice
地球の平和を守るのさ
We'll protect the peace of the world
探険しようぜ
Let's go on an adventure
お化け屋敷
In the haunted house
でも本当は
But in truth...
怖くて泣き虫
...I'm a scaredy-cat crybaby
一緒にいたいだけ
I just want to be with you
明日も晴れて
If tomorrow is clear too
空を青く照らせば
And the sky is lit up blue
僕らはここに
Let's build a...
秘密基地を作ろう
...secret base here
そして探険しよう
And then, let's explore
雨ならゲームをしよう
If it rains, let's play games
そんな時間が
That kind of time...
ずっと続くはずだったんだ
...was supposed to last forever
そう
That's right
悪者は僕だった
I was the bad guy
行けたならば僕は
If I could have gone, I...
嘘じゃない 本当の嘘つきだった
...wouldn't have lied, but I was a real liar.
花束に包まれて 目を瞑る君は
Wrapped in a bouquet, as you close your eyes,
安らかに 清らかに 眠っていたんだ
You were sleeping peacefully and purely.
変わらぬ感情が いつか君を消していく
Unchanging feelings will one day erase you.
失う前に 冷えてしまう前に
Before I lose you, before it gets cold.
何度願ったって 仏は来ていなかった
No matter how many times I prayed, Buddha never came.
きっと僕たちは 出会う時が来る きっと
Surely the time will come for us to meet. Surely.
Yippee!
Hello! You want some marshmallows?
I heard marshmallows!
Marshmallows!
マシュマロだって！
She said marshmallows!
マシュマロ！
Marshmallow!
マシュマロだって！
She said marshmallows!
マシュマロ！
Marshmallow!
食べていいの？
Can we eat them?
Can we eat?
Really?!
やっほー！
Yay!
My marshmallow!
Marshmallow party!
じゃあ一緒に、乾杯！
Then, together... Cheers!
乾杯！
Cheers!
Marshmallow-chan!
Let's go!
キャンプファイヤー！
Campfire!
Fire!
Fire! Fire marshmallow!
Are you gonna roast marshmallows?
I'm amazing at it.
Fire marshmallow!
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
Amazing!
Let's go!
いい感じじゃない？いい感じじゃない？
Doesn't it look good? Doesn't it look good?
美味しい！
Delicious!
What is this? What is this?
What is this? This is perfection.
わくわく！
Exciting!
ごくごくじゃない？ Perfect!
Isn't it "gulp gulp"? Perfect!
Shall we eat?
いただきます！
Let's eat!
Mamma mia!
How's your marshmallow?
Very smoky.
うまい！
Tasty!
ちょうどいい。
Just right.
あーん！
Aaah!
美味しい？
Is it delicious?
美味しい！
It's delicious!
ごちそうさまでした。
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでした！
Thank you for the meal!
じゃあ一緒に、レッツ・シング・ア・ソング！
Then, together... Let's sing a song!
Yeah! Next song!
夏の日と君の声
Natsu no Hi to Kimi no Koe
Lyrics:ChouCho Music:渡辺拓也
Lyrics: ChouCho, Music: Takuya Watanabe
追いかけても 追いかけても
Even if I chase after it, even if I chase after it
届かない 雲のような
Like a cloud that's out of reach
言葉で 表せない
A feeling that can't be expressed
感情 見つけたよ
In words, I found it
胸の中で ざわめいてる
Rustling inside my chest
波の 本当の意味を
The true meaning of the waves
日差しに 遮られて
Obstructed by the sunlight
私は まだ知らない
I still don't know
あの頃 描いた
What I drew back then
絵日記みたい
Like a picture diary
すべてが 色づき始める
Everything starts to change color
ほら
Look
真夏の空と 海の青さに
In the midsummer sky and the blue of the sea
まぶしくて 目を閉じても
Even if I close my eyes because it's so bright
私の 心の端っこを
The corner of my heart
つかんで 離さない
You grabbed it and won't let go
君の声は
Your voice is...
これが 恋かな
Could this be love?
自転車を押し 歩く君の
As you walk pushing your bicycle
隣で その横顔
Next to you, that profile
そっと 見つめていると
When I gaze at you softly
呼吸を 忘れてしまう
I forget to breathe
子供の頃 見た
Like the kaleidoscope
万華鏡のように
I saw when I was a child
明日が くるくる変わっていく
Tomorrow keeps on changing
ほら
Look
真夏の太陽に 照らされて
Illuminated by the midsummer sun
焼きつくような 痛みも
Even the burning pain
嬉しさも 切なさも全部
Happiness and sadness, all of it
初めて 出会いたい
I want to meet for the first time
切ない気持ち
This painful feeling
失くしたくない
I don't want to lose it
どうしてだろう もっと 知りたくなる
I wonder why I want to know more
君の
About you
鼓動
About your heartbeat
自分自身のこと
About myself
真夏の空と 海の青さに
In the midsummer sky and the blue of the sea
まぶしくて 目を閉じても
Even if I close my eyes because it's so bright
私の 心の端っこを
The corner of my heart
つかんで 離さない
You grabbed it and won't let go
君の声は
Your voice is...
優しく響く
Echoing softly
そして
And
恋が始まる
Love begins
I MET A BEAR
The other day
I met a bear
Up in the woods
Away up there
The other day I met a bear,
up in the woods away up there.
He looked at me
I looked at him
He sized me up
I sized him up
He looked at me, I looked at him,
he sized me up, I sized him up.
He said to me
Why don't you run
I see you don't
Have any gun
He said to me why don't you run,
I see you don't have any gun.
And so I ran
Away from there
And right behind
There was a bear
And so I ran away from there,
and right behind there was a bear.
Ahead of me
I saw a tree
A great big tree
Oh golly gee
Ahead of me I saw a tree,
a great big tree, oh golly gee.
The lowest branch
Was ten feet up
I had to jump
And trust my luck
The lowest branch was ten feet up,
I had to jump and trust my luck.
And so I jumped
Into the air
But I missed that branch
Away up there
And so I jumped into the air,
but I missed that branch away up there.
Now don't you fret
And don't you frown
I caught that branch
On the way back down
Now don't you fret and don't you frown,
I caught that branch on the way back down.
That's all there is
There ain't no more
Until I meet
That bear once more
That's all there is there ain't no more,
until I meet that bear once more.
The end, the end
The end, the end, the end, the end,
the end, the end, the end, the end.
the end, the end, the end, the end!
ちいさな冒険者
Little Adventurer
Lyrics / Music : 佐藤良成
Lyrics / Music: Yoshinari Sato
転んで擦りむいたとこ
The place where I fell and scraped myself
血がにじんでしみるけれど
It's bleeding a bit and it stings, but...
へっちゃらさ すぐ治るから
It's no big deal, it'll heal right away
明日にはかさぶたできる
By tomorrow, it'll be a scab
今日もまたバカにされたよ
Today they made fun of me again
はずかしいし悔しいけれど
It's embarrassing and frustrating, but...
へっちゃらさ 覚えておけよ
It's no big deal, you just wait
今に笑い返してやる
I'll be the one laughing later
岬から舟を出せば
When we set sail from the cape
風を受けて帆が膨らむ
The sails swell as they catch the wind
ぼくら今 土地を離れ
We're leaving this land behind now
七つの海を股にかける
To travel across the seven seas
いつか 残したとこ
The spot left behind someday
むらさき色 あざになった
Has turned into a purple bruise
へっちゃらさ 今日のところは
I'm fine, for today
負けだっこ たんにしておいてやる
I'll just let it be a loss for now
丘に立ち 手を広げて
Standing on a hill, spreading my arms
風を待ち 羽ばたくのさ
Waiting for the wind, I'll take flight
僕は今 土を離れ
I am now leaving the earth
お大空 渡るひばり
A skylark crossing the vast sky
南から
From the south
風が吹いて
A wind blows
急に雨
Suddenly it
降りはじめた
started to rain
春はすぐ
Spring is
隣にいる
right there next to us
洗濯物 取り込まなくちゃ
I have to bring in the laundry
Oh hi everybody! I hope that you
have enjoyed this beautiful night/morning so far.
I think you know what time it is now.
Time to pull out the number one businesswoman
of Hololive English.
Oh hi! I am Nanashi Mumei from Hololive English Promise.
This is the part of the stream where I tell you
about the birthday merchandise.
I will show you now. Over here. こちら！
I will show you now. Over here. Right here!
Birthday Celebration 2024
Tada! My birthday merchandise is camp-themed!
Who could have assumed this?
Yes, yes, yes.
I, instead of reading this here, which I could totally do...
...let's just go ahead and show you the first thing.
Next, or first, is... こちら！
Next, or first, is... here!
Campin' Tapestry
Here we have a Campin' Tapestry.
That is right. It's a tapestry of me, Mumei,
campin' for you.
For your wall. Make way if your walls
are covered in things.
If your wall is empty, you are so welcome.
It's a B2-sized tapestry.
Uh, I think... I really like the art. It's super, super pretty.
And, I don't know, maybe it can inspire you to go outside...
...and look at the stars.
Or maybe it can make you grateful that you have
a roof over your head.
There's a lot, lots of things you can do with this.
Mhm. Next up is... こちら！
Mhm. Next up is... here!
MOOM Cap
A hat! A cap! A MOOM Cap!
Called this because it says "MOOM" on it.
What else is there? There is a little owl face. Do you see that?
Do you see that in the "MOOM"? It has my feathers.
You can really tell it's Moom.
Mhm. Yeah. Uh, I don't know, I feel like hats are pretty nice, pretty useful.
You wear them on your head. You can wear them
in whatever direction you so please.
Uh, yeah, really up to you. You have a lot of freedom with this one.
Uh, yeah. Next is... こちら！
Uh, yeah. Next is... here!
It's A Compact Wallet
It's a compact wal— I... I forgot I named it that.
It is. It is a compact wallet.
Uh, yeah. Uh... do we still use wallets today?
I guess we do. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you can put uh, money, cards, coins
if you still use those for some reason.
Or... oh! Pro tip! Pro tip from me, Nanashi Mumei...
...the number one businesswoman of Hololive English.
Maybe even Holo— I should probably shouldn't say that.
Uh, you can also use it for the money that you can save...
...from combining your purchase, bundling it with other merchandise...
...which will reduce the shipping cost!
Pro tip from— I... I said this already.
Just... just a little advice. Just putting that out there.
Uh, yeah. Nice wallet for money.
Next up is... こちら！
Next up is... here!
Mumei's Guitar Pick Keychain
Mumei's Guitar Pick Keychain.
That's right, you can get one of the thousands of guitar picks...
...that I own, that, uh, is like the one that I used today...
...in this live, playing guitar.
Uh, yeah, so you can actually remove the pick from the keychain...
...and use it to play— play guitar.
ムメイのギターピックキーホルダー
Mumei's Guitar Pick Keychain
Or maybe use it for your— like you could use it as a toothpick maybe, I don't know, maybe thin enough...
...depends how— how big the gaps in your teeth are.
Uh, yeah! Functional pick! Real pick!
Nice. Picks are nice.
Uh, and then finally is...
こちら。
...this.
The bonus! The bonus item! We have a Polaroid again this year.
And like always, there is a limited one... Uh, if you buy the full set...
...you can get a truly signed Nanashi Mumei Polaroid.
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
Ah, but do not fret if you are not able to get the limited set, you can get a printed signature...
...of mine, me, Nanashi Mumei.
Uh, yeah. This is if you buy the full set, if you want this.
And this is everything all together. Oh, it's so pleasing to look at when it's in a— in a set.
Yes, that's the word. A set, complete set like this.
Yes, hopefully there's something you like, something you could use...
誕生日記念フルセット
Birthday Merch Complete Set
...useful for you, something you can enjoy and cherish.
Yes. Anyways, uh...
...it will be available as soon as the live ends.
So really, pay attention. Pay attention to when I am gone, out of here.
I pulled an all-nighter, didn't I? The— the sun is rising in the east.
I think I got one more song left in me before I have to crash into that tent there.
How are you guys holding up? Good for one more song?
Yeah, you are!
All right, all right, let's get— let me get ready and hope this doesn't take too much time. Okay, okay.
I'll get ready. Where's... Where's my guitar? Oh, find it. Oh, it's there.
遠い遠い　笑えない話
A distant, distant, unfunny story
いつか僕が　いなくなったなら
If one day I were to disappear
深い深い　森に落ちた
You fell into a deep, deep forest
君は独りで　行くんだぜ
You're going to go alone
繋いだ手には　柔らかな体温
In our joined hands was a soft warmth
握った指が　ゆるり解けたら
When our held fingers slowly unraveled
枯れた音色の　鐘が鳴る
The bell with a withered tone rings
君は独りで　行くんだぜ
You're going to go alone
そのまま二人　歩んで一人
Just like that, the two of us walking, then one
嘘つく声も　持て余したままに
With the voice that tells lies still out of hand
俯き二人　影が一つ
Looking down, the two of us, one shadow
僕も独りで　行くんだぜ
I'm also going to go alone
君は淡い　恋に落ちた
You fell into a faint love
高い高い　崖に咲く花
A flower blooming on a high, high cliff
届かないんだ　焦がれて犠牲に
I can't reach it, yearning and sacrificing
今度は独りで　行くんだぜ
This time you're going to go alone
…はない話
...not a... story.
いつか僕がいなくなったなら
If one day I'm no longer here,
世界深い森に落ちた
the world will fall into a deep forest.
君は一人で行くんだぜ
You will have to go on alone.
それから一人歩いて
And then, walking alone,
一人嘘つく
telling lies to yourself,
子供も疲れた
you grew tired of being a child.
うつむき一人 黄金の部屋
Hanging your head alone in a golden room,
君と二人でいたんだぜ
I was there together with you.
僕は深い森に落ちた
I fell into the deep forest.
クロッカス透けて
Looking through the crocuses,
汚れた果実
at the soiled fruit.
それでおしまい それだけの話
That's the end, just that story.
君は一人で行くんだぜ
You will have to go on alone.
Outside THE BOX
Nanashi Mumei 3D Birthday Live 2024
七詩ムメイ3D生誕祭ライブ2024
Outside THE BOX
Nanashi Mumei 3D Birthday Live 2024